Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation Records UA042
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Surveys and reports, 1900 -- 2007; 1965 -- 1999; UA042.001; 56.4 Linear Feet; 139 Digital Object(s)
  - Dental: Comparisons, 1986 -- 1987; UA042.001.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - Dental School: Correlation Study, 1986; UA042.001.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - Enrollment Management, McGuire Report, 1986; UA042.001.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - Dental: Fact Book, 1974; UA042.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - TUSDM [Tufts University School of Dental Medicine], Acceptance Stage Competitors, 1984 -- 1986; UA042.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Dental: Admissions, 1984; UA042.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Dental: Admissions MArketing, 1984 -- 1987; UA042.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Dental: Attrition, 1986 -- 1987; UA042.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Dental: Admission Acceptances, 1988; UA042.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Fifth-Year Report to the New England Association of Schools, 1987; UA042.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher School: Ten-Year Comparision, 1964 -- 1975; UA042.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher School: Enrollment, 1982; UA042.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher School: Overseas Outreach, n.d., UA042.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Fletcher, History, 1975; UA042.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Fletcher, Fact Sheet, 1981; UA042.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Fletcher, Student Body Size, 1982; UA042.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Fletcher, 1985; UA042.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Academic Difficulty, Requests for Data, 1987; UA042.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Academic Difficulty Study, 1987; UA042.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Academic Difficulty, 1986; UA042.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Academic Difficulty, 1980; UA042.001.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Academic Difficulty, Literature Review, 1986; UA042.001.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher Admissions, 1970 -- 1971; UA042.001.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Veterinary School, Comparative Study, 1986; UA042.001.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Comparison - Classification and Comparative Institutions, 1984; UA042.001.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Comparison, 1984; UA042.001.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Arts & Sciences Engineering Study Materials, 1983; UA042.001.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Arts & Sciences Engineering Task Force, 1974 -- 1975; UA042.001.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Arts & Sciences Engineering Study Materials, 1983; UA042.001.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Arts & Sciences Engineering Study Materials, 1983; UA042.001.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - Engineering Enrollment by Area, 1980; UA042.001.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Accreditation Engineering, 1972; UA042.001.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Accreditation Engineering, 1976; UA042.001.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Arts & Science Engineering Admissions, 1981; UA042.001.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Arts & Science, B.S. Engineering Physics, 1983; UA042.001.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Arts & Science, Cooperative Engineering Tuition, 1983; UA042.001.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Arts & Science Development Plan for Engineering, 1983; UA042.001.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Arts & Science Workload, Courses, 1972; UA042.001.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Arts & Science, Faculty Workload, 1975; UA042.001.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - Faculty Workload, 1981; UA042.001.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - Undergraduate Student Quality, 1983; UA042.001.007.00038 (Box 7)
  - Facilities: Arts & Science, Faculty, 1985; UA042.001.007.00039 (Box 7)
  - Faculty & Staff: Arts & Science, Misc. Faculty Statistics, 1976 -- 1981; UA042.001.007.00040 (Box 7)
  - Faculty & Staff: Arts & Science, Planning Materials "Redbook: 1979", UA042.001.007.00041 (Box 7)
  - Faculty & Staff: Arts & Science, Faculty Scholarships and Quality Study, 1976; UA042.001.007.00042 (Box 7)
  - Faculty & Staff: Arts & Science, Class Sizes Fall, 1970; UA042.001.007.00043 (Box 7)
  - Faculty: Arts & Science Faculty Salaries, 1985 -- 1986; UA042.001.007.00044 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Accreditation University, 1970; UA042.001.007.00045 (Box 7)
  - Programs: Accreditation University, 1980 -- 1981; UA042.001.007.00046 (Box 7)
  - Admissions Survey, Frequencies Matriculants Fletcher, 1991; UA042.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Admissions Survey, Frequencies Non-Matriculants Fletcher, 1992; UA042.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey, Fletcher, 1992; UA042.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Programs: Accreditation University, 1982 -- 1987; UA042.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Dental Pew Proposal, 1982; UA042.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Report to the President, 1986; UA042.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Frequencies Fletcher (2/2), 1992; UA042.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Frequencies and Tables Fletcher Preview, 1992; UA042.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - Rejected Applicant Survey Fletcher, 1990; UA042.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - APSIA Schools Survey Fletcher (2/2), 1989; UA042.001.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Frequencies Fletcher, 1989; UA042.001.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey, Matric and Nonmatric Fletcher, 1988; UA042.001.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Survey, Data Entry - Folder 0, 1988; UA042.001.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Survey, Data Entry - Folder 1, 1988; UA042.001.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Frequencies Fletcher, 1988; UA042.001.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Accepted App. Survey Instrument Fletcher, 1987; UA042.001.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey Fletcher, 1987; UA042.001.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Accepted App. Study: Factors that Influence Selection, 1998; UA042.001.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Correspondence and Misc., 1992; UA042.001.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence - Tufts, 1990 -- 1991; UA042.001.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - Timetable [Tufts Self Study], 1990; UA042.001.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - Committee Members, 1990; UA042.001.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Steering Committee, 1991; UA042.001.008.00025 (Box 8)
  - Institutional Data Forms + Back Up from Registrar, 1990; UA042.001.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - Interim Self-Study Guide, 1992; UA042.001.008.00027 (Box 8)
  - [Accreditation Handbook], 1989; UA042.001.008.00028 (Box 8)
  - Accreditation - Misc. Important, 1992; UA042.001.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - Final Self-Study Copy [Part I-VI], 1992; UA042.001.008.00030 (Box 8)
  - Final Self-Study Copy [Part VII to end], 1992; UA042.001.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - Final Report of the Visiting Team, 1992; UA042.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Accreditation Originals of Final Self-Study Report [I-VI], 1992; UA042.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Surveys and Assessment, 1990; UA042.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Support, 1988; UA042.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Outcomes - Comments, 1988; UA042.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Outcomes, 1988; UA042.001.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Alumni - Class of 1982 By Ethnicity, UA042.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Class of 1982 By College, UA042.001.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Class of [19]82 By Major, UA042.001.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Alumni - Class of 1982 All Responses - Frequencies, UA042.001.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - American Studies, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Art History, 1994; UA042.001.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Biology, 1993; UA042.001.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Chemistry, 1993; UA042.001.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Classics, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Child Study, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - English, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Community Health, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Computer Science, 1994; UA042.001.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Drama/Dance [Course Offerings], 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Economics [Courses], 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Environmental Studies [Courses], 1993; UA042.001.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Experimental College [Courses], 1993; UA042.001.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Geology [Courses], 1994; UA042.001.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - German/Russian/Asian Studies [Courses], 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - History [Courses], 1993 -- 1995; UA042.001.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - International Relations [Courses], 1992 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Mathematics [Courses], 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - Music [Courses], 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Peace & Justice Studies [Courses], 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - Philosophy Department [Courses], 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - Physical Education [Courses], 1994; UA042.001.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Physics and Astronomy [Courses], 1994; UA042.001.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - Political Science [Courses], 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - Pre-Med Requirements, 1991 -- 1992; UA042.001.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - Psychology [Courses], 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - Religion [Courses], 1992 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00038 (Box 9)
  - Romance Languages [Courses], 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - Sociology/Anthropology [Courses], 1992 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - Studio Arts [Courses], 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - Women's Studies [Courses], 1994; UA042.001.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - Study Abroad [Guidelines, Programs], 1992 -- 1995; UA042.001.009.00043 (Box 9)
  - World Civilization [Courses], 1992 -- 1994; UA042.001.009.00044 (Box 9)
  - Writing Workshops [Courses], 1993 -- 1995; UA042.001.009.00045 (Box 9)
  - American Studies [Courses], 1995 -- 1997; UA042.001.009.00046 (Box 9)
  - Art History [Courses], 1995; UA042.001.009.00047 (Box 9)
  - Biology [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.009.00048 (Box 9)
  - Child Study [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.009.00049 (Box 9)
  - Chemistry [Courses], 1995; UA042.001.009.00050 (Box 9)
  - Classics [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.009.00051 (Box 9)
  - Community Health, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.009.00052 (Box 9)
  - Computer Science [Courses], 1995; UA042.001.009.00053 (Box 9)
  - Drama/Dance [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Economics [Courses], 1995; UA042.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Education [Courses, Handbook], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - English [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Environmental Studies [Courses, Programs], 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Geology [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - German/Russian/Asian [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - History [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - International Relations [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Mathematics [Courses], 1995; UA042.001.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Music [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Museum School [Courses], 1996; UA042.001.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Philosophy [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - Peace and Justice Studies [Courses], 1995; UA042.001.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Political Science [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Psychology [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Physics/Astronomy [Courses], 1995; UA042.001.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - Physical Education [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - Religion [Courses], 1994; UA042.001.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - Study Abroad [Programs], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - Romance Languages [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - Sociology/Anthropology [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - Studio Arts [Courses], 1995; UA042.001.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - Women's Studies [Courses], 1996; UA042.001.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - World Civilization [Courses], 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - Writing Workshops [Courses], 1995 -- 1997; UA042.001.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - Senior Survey Reports, Evaluation of Advising (1), 1993; UA042.001.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - Senior Survey Reports, Evaluation of Advising, (2), 1993; UA042.001.010.00028 (Box 10)
  - Senior Survey Reports, Evaluation of Advising, 1993; UA042.001.010.00029 (Box 10)
  - Actual Majors by Intended, Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.010.00030 (Box 10)
  - Actual Majors by Intended, Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.010.00031 (Box 10)
  - Intended Major by Actual Majors, Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.010.00032 (Box 10)
  - Intended Major by Actual Majors, Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.010.00033 (Box 10)
  - Senior Survey Class of 1993, Intended Major by Actual Major by Ethnicity, UA042.001.010.00034 (Box 10)
  - Senior Survey Class of 1993, Intended Major by Actual Major by Ethnicity, UA042.001.010.00035 (Box 10)
  - Senior Survey Class of 1993, Intended Major by Actual Major by Ethnicity, UA042.001.010.00036 (Box 10)
  - Senior Survey Repot, Evaluation of Minors, 1993; UA042.001.010.00037 (Box 10)
  - Senior Survey Report, General Evaluation of Study Abroad, 1993; UA042.001.010.00038 (Box 10)
  - Senior Survey Report, Evaluation of Certificate Programs, 1993; UA042.001.010.00039 (Box 10)
  - Senior Survey Report, Transfer Student Evaluation, 1993; UA042.001.010.00040 (Box 10)
  - Trends, 1993; UA042.001.010.00041 (Box 10)
  - Six-Year Summary of Post-Graduate Plans, 1988 -- 1993; UA042.001.010.00042 (Box 10)
  - Additional Comments, Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.010.00043 (Box 10)
  - Major Challenge facing Tufts, Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.010.00044 (Box 10)
  - If you had to do it over again...Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.010.00045 (Box 10)
  - Senior Survey Report, Importance of Services, 1993; UA042.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey Report, 1993; UA042.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey Report, Importance of Services, 1993; UA042.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey Report, Evaluation of Finances, 1993; UA042.001.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Data Request, 1988 -- 1990; UA042.001.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Intended vs. Actual Majors Cumulative, 1990 -- 1991; UA042.001.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Additional Senior Survey Analysis 1991 [W. Swap's requested material], 1993; UA042.001.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey, Responses by "College", 1991; UA042.001.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey, Responses by "Race", 1991; UA042.001.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals - "Responses by Gender", 1991; UA042.001.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey, Meetings, 1991; UA042.001.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey, Correspondence, 1991; UA042.001.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals Q51. "What is the one experience that had the greatest impact on your experience at Tufts?", 1992; UA042.001.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals Q51. "What is the one experience that had the greatest impact on your experience at Tufts?", 1992; UA042.001.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey, Letters, 1991; UA042.001.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey, Timetable, 1991; UA042.001.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey, Instrument, 1991; UA042.001.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey Preview, 1991; UA042.001.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey "Major by Ethnicity", 1991; UA042.001.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey Reports, 1991; UA042.001.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Originals - Instrument, 1991; UA042.001.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Post-Graduate Plans, 1991; UA042.001.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey List of Students Interested in Alumni Network, 1991; UA042.001.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey, Code Book, 1991; UA042.001.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey Comparative Data, 1990; UA042.001.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - Computer Services and Campus Safety, Senior Survey, 1990; UA042.001.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey "One experience or individual who has had the greatest impact on experience at Tufts.", 1991; UA042.001.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey "What is the one experience or individual who has had the greatest impact on experience at Tufts.", 1991; UA042.001.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by Gender", 1992; UA042.001.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by College", 1994; UA042.001.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey Responses by GPA Ranges, 1992; UA042.001.011.00031 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey Summary of Responses Re:Satisfaction, 1992; UA042.001.011.00032 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey "Responses by interest in joining alumni career advisory network.", 1992; UA042.001.011.00033 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by willingness to recommend Tufts to high school students.", 1992; UA042.001.011.00034 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by Tufts alumni - admissions program.", 1992; UA042.001.011.00035 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by Race", 1992; UA042.001.011.00036 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by concern regarding educational debts.", 1992; UA042.001.011.00037 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey "Responses regarding advisors.", 1992; UA042.001.011.00038 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by Study Abroad", 1992; UA042.001.011.00039 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by fall employment activity.", 1992; UA042.001.011.00040 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by Major Areas", 1992; UA042.001.011.00041 (Box 11)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by overall satisfaction", 1992; UA042.001.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by academic challenge rating", 1992; UA042.001.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Senior Survey, Responses by "Interest in attending alumni activities", 1992; UA042.001.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Senior Survey "Graduate study area by gender & ethnicity", 1992; UA042.001.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by interest in planning alumni activities", 1992; UA042.001.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by grad school attendance", 1992; UA042.001.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Senior Survey - Originals "Responses by highest level of education planned", 1992; UA042.001.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Intended Major by Primary Major, Class of, 1992; UA042.001.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Evaluation of Majors, Senior Survey (1), 1992; UA042.001.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Evaluation of Majors, Senior Survey (2), 1992; UA042.001.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - Evaluation of Majors, Senior Survey (3), 1992; UA042.001.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Evaluation of Majors, Senior Survey (4), 1992; UA042.001.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Evaluation of Majors, Senior Survey (5), 1992; UA042.001.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - Network, TAAP, and Alumni Activities Documents, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - "Majors by Gender and Race" Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Summaries Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Senior Survey [Diskette], 1992; UA042.001.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Originals Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Timetable Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Meetings, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Evaluation of Undergraduate Majors, TABLES, MEANS Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Correspondences, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - Preview Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - Correspondences and Meetings, Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - Timetable Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00025 (Box 12)
  - Survey Instrument Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00026 (Box 12)
  - Hughes Found Request Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00027 (Box 12)
  - Originals Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00028 (Box 12)
  - Alumni Activity, Question 85 Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00029 (Box 12)
  - Alumni Network, Question 83 Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00030 (Box 12)
  - Alumni Career Advisory Network, Question 82 Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00031 (Box 12)
  - Five-Year Post-Graduate Plans, 1988 -- 1993; UA042.001.012.00032 (Box 12)
  - Post-Graduate Plans Class of, 1993; UA042.001.012.00033 (Box 12)
  - Primary Major Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00034 (Box 12)
  - Satisfaction with by Race, Gender, College & GPA Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00035 (Box 12)
  - Evaluation of Majors Senior Survey (1), 1993; UA042.001.012.00036 (Box 12)
  - Evaluation of Majors Senior Survey (2), 1993; UA042.001.012.00037 (Box 12)
  - Evaluation of Majors Senior Survey (3), 1993; UA042.001.012.00038 (Box 12)
  - Evaluation of Majors Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00039 (Box 12)
  - "If you had to do it over again, would you attend Tufts?" Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00040 (Box 12)
  - Requirements Senior Survey, 1993; UA042.001.012.00041 (Box 12)
  - Comments Senior Survey, 1990; UA042.001.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - One experience having the greatest impact, Senior Survey, 1991; UA042.001.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - Important Aspect of Experience at Tufts, Senior Survey, 1991; UA042.001.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Evaluation of Undergraduate Majors, Senior Survey, 1991; UA042.001.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Responses by Race, Senior Survey, 1991; UA042.001.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Responses by College Senior Survey, 1991; UA042.001.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Responses by Gender Senior Survey, 1991; UA042.001.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Evaluation of Undergraduate Majors, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Responses by willingness to recommend Tufts to high school seniors, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Responses by Study Abroad, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - One experience with greatest impact on experience at Tufts, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Responses by Race Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Frequency by College, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Frequencies, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Frequency by Gender Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Tables, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Responses by College Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Responses by Overall Satisfaction, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - Responses by willingness to recommend Tufts to high school seniors, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Responses by Major Areas, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Responses by Overall Satisfaction, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00021 (Box 13)
  - Responses by Graduate School Attendance, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00022 (Box 13)
  - Responses by Interest in Attending Alumni Activities, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00023 (Box 13)
  - Responses by Race, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.013.00024 (Box 13)
  - Respnses by GPA Ranges Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Responses by Highest Level of Education Planned, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - Responses by College Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Responses by interst in attending alumni activites, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Responses by Academic Challenge Rating, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Responses by Fall Employment Activity, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Responses by interest in joining the alumni career advisory network, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Responses by Study Abroad, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Responses by Concern Regarding Educational Debt, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - Responses by Highest Level of Education Planned, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Responses by Gender, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Reponses by Graduate School Attendance, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Responses by Interest in Tufts Alumni Admissions Program, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Responses by Interest in Planning Alumni Activities, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Responses by Major Areas, Senior Survey, 1992; UA042.001.014.00015 (Box 14)